I think the biggest thing
is just recognizing that
we're going to have AI forever.
like there's no getting away
from any of that we really
need to find a way to
harness the power that it has
to make us more like
effective and efficient
you don't know how to use
it you're going to fall
behind that being said if
that's all you use you're
useless because anyone can use AI
these are the three questions we'll talk
about.
So kind of keep these in mind while we're
going through.
Like an experience where
use of AI has helped
you learn something or
has been productive.
A time when it's felt uneasy,
unproductive, or crippling.
Maybe that's an extreme word,
but I'm having trouble
thinking of a synonym.
Then what kind of lab culture would you
support establishing any specifics?
In this instance, AI
was able to run a test
for me and collect data.
This will be very helpful because it can
run 24 So Tim's on at Claude, can you pick
up, move, run the following Google Cloud
code, post here the
results, and then return
the enclosure.
So it's giving it this code here.
And Claude took 42 minutes, picked it up,
sensor test ran, went down mid
like, if I had an e -bike,
I know myself well enough
that I would probably start
relying on the e -bike
intensively rather than
getting a workout that I need
every day, And so it's so
much easier to be complacent
when the tool is there.
not like we can choose to
not buy the e -bike right
it's the yeah it's like the
e -bike is there yes and
And like, oh, sorry, I bought it.
Yeah, I bought it for all this.
I literally bought it for everybody.
And the question I ask is,
how important is it for
us as students going into
the professional world soon
to be competent in not
only using AI, but using AI
fruitfully,
But, you know, he uses
his AI Jarvis to also,
you know, be his tool to,
you know, be there to run
the tests that he already
worked out or to support
his reasoning or stuff like that.
So kind of like that way
where Jarvis is a support
to Tony Stark and not
doing Tony Stark's work.
It relates a lot to how we've
learned things in general,
like all through school,
we taught how to do math,
and only after you understand
how to do that, then
you get to calculate
We're supposed to be things
that act and not to be
acted upon If we start using
AI too much then AI starts
using us and that should
be the other way around
give it a baseline.
Like, here's what I'm thinking.
Is there something wrong
with what I'm thinking?
How could this be improved?
I think like people coming
into the lab in a semester
when things have been
built, and they're just kind
of like, I never got the
chance to learn any of this.
Claude has been
controlling the whole thing
writing the code that does the tests and
running the tests The scary part of that
is I have not done that
and I don't currently
know like if you asked me to do it myself
I couldn't do it right now it would take
me a couple days probably that's scary
that's one of the limits I
think that AI has is it's
not very good at generating
those structures that
we need.
Yeah, like generating images
and like spatial awareness
AI is very poor at.
It does really well with
like analyzing information
and like things to do with
like words and things like
that.
It goes very good at image
analysis, spatial analysis,
things like that.
It's not there.
Yeah, it doesn't live in the three.
world with us.
It's all just code and stuff.
I'm just wondering, would
it be helpful, like when
new people come into the lab,
we would run them through,
hey, this is good ways to be using AI?
like using it to teach
you to do things and using
it to maybe like debug
stuff like we need some kind
of like tutorial to show people
Yeah, I like that, Audrey.
That gets me thinking, we
can probably pull some of
the things from this discussion.
I think I can add, probably
add this in with one of
those kind of like onboarding things.
Or maybe I missed heard
Audrey, but I think I heard
her say real.
So like, you know, we could
make like a real of us
like being, this is good.
this is bad
Okay, we'll probably call it good there.
Thanks, Audrey Carl, everybody.